You guys have looked [clears throat] at
everything all the entire all the
activity you guys have done you know
with the roster really before this first
two days.
How much more
better do you feel about where this
roster is as you you know kind of take
the next step forward?
Feel great.
Addressing the receiver room and the old
line room along with the safety
position.
Um
you know, I think we're as we went into
the draft and I think Andrew can speak
to this more than I can but
uh
it's where we hoped we would head
where we would address. Is Austin Barber
a tackle or could he move inside? See
him as a tackle to start obviously has
some flex we think could move inside.
Talk about you know back-to-back
receivers in the first and second round
that's doesn't happen often so
what is your reaction to get those two
guys?
Well, they compliments if you take
Denzel after Casey I think he
compliments Casey. He's a different body
type than what we have.
Uh we were looking at uh
someone we thought could be a size
match-up and especially in the red zone
which we did not have. So loved his
competitive spirit
uh I just talking about Denzel now spoke
with Jed Fisch his head coach at
Washington who I've got a ton of respect
for been in the NFL and and raved about
Denzel.
Loves to practice competitive
a lot of fight in him has come a long
way as a player and uh is only going to
continue to get better and we certainly
needed to to continue to upgrade that
position and we did.
Feeling coming out you know I know you
guys gained this house feeling Andrew
and Matt but like to come out of this
draft with four players in the first two
nights that a lot of folks had first
round grades on.
Well
I mean ultimately now whether we take
him in the first round second round
third round wherever their grades are
now it's up to us as a coaching staff to
develop them and that's why we're hired
that's why coaches are hired as to
develop the players that show up in your
locker room.
And uh
you know, you're always trying to
maximize a player's measurable skill set
and that's what we're that's what we're
going to fight like hell to do.
Still kind of a hole in the middle of
your offensive line I know a lot of you
think he can go there but how much
discussion in the draft room has there
been about the center position? There
has been and
um there's a possibility we'll still
address that as we get further into the
draft.
Everybody's tired I get it I'm tired
too. I know you talked about
Denzel's red zone ability how important
was it to have two receivers that have
like a complimentary skill sets to do
what you want to do offensively?
Probably more important than usual just
to the makeup of our
receiver room as it sits right now would
not have been as big a deal
um if you would have had some bigger
body types but you when you look at some
of the body types we have when we take
the field every day we certainly needed
to
um
certainly get bigger we certainly needed
to add
um some size to that room and uh you
know, Denzel provided that for us. You
got a question for the Andrew but
kind of unusual to trade out of the
round and then to come back in with
Austin and Matt. It was a lot of fun.
I mean it was a heck of a ride.
I was just in there for the ride so it
was pretty cool.
You talking about are you talking about
Barber? Yeah. No, I mean we really liked
him from the jump.
Um you don't know how the board again
Andrew can answer this you don't know in
my limited experience of of this you
don't know how it's going to go there's
certain players that are picked higher
than you would have thought and there's
others that are a little bit lower
certainly we knew we had to address
uh the offensive line.
And so
you know, as it as
as he was still up on the board I think
the opportunity to move back and then as
it as it continued then let's not wait
any longer let's go up and get him and
we're fired up to get him. When you look
at the competition now in the receiver
room what what do you see in total
there?
Well, I just think you have to keep
adding to the room as best you can
you're trying to raise the floor mean
ultimately at any position group you
start by raising the floor
and developing who you have and that
started this past week so
it just turned out
the way the draft unfolded and Andrew
again can speak to this that when we got
to you know, the spot that we had at
seven would be actually 39 but today
seven
we did have opportunities and Andrew
will speak to it to move back but we
really thought at that pick take Denzel.
How do you feel with the guys that you
added with the guys you had with Gerald
do you feel pretty good about the
potential explosiveness of your offense?
I feel better.
You mentioned safety being something you
guys are obviously looking at on the
other side of things just what what
strikes you and stands out about
Emmanuel Moseley Warren and what do you
like with with what he brings to the
table?
Um
length speed tough.
That's it. I mean he's got great length
excellent speed and he'll hit that guy
to you I mean that's three pretty good
characteristics of a safety. Yes
yesterday so I asked you guys today were
you kind of surprised in how the board
fell today in getting Denzel with a
first round grade? Uh surprised to I
would not say that I I would not say
that.
Of of the picks
I would not say
uh that I was surprised especially on
the offensive guys. If you asked me
where those picks went
uh I would have said it was you know
pretty close to where we kind of had
targeted where we thought they they
would be available. Again Andrew can
speak to that I'm speaking for me.
You know, in terms of where I would have
thought
uh
cuz I did evaluate all those players and
I would have said that was about right
and the board actually played out that
way. How much more fun is it
doing this if fun's the right word doing
this as a head coach instead of
offensive coordinator?
Well
I have one more level
of input I guess
as opposed to
a step down you know, from the head
coach end of the OC
but
um ultimately
it's more fun cuz um
you know, when you're an offensive
coordinator you're really not
responsible for winning you're
responsible for scoring.
And when you're the head coach we're
responsible for winning so I certainly
want to score
but uh more importantly we got to win
football games and so when it came down
to
you know, when you're talking about
defensive players I'm all for great
defensive players going to help us win
ultimately that's our job as an
organization the head coach is to do
everything in our power
to put a roster together gives us a
chance to compete every week and
ultimately
turn this organization into a consistent
winning one.
Mentioned how your messaging about what
type of players you want is really
direct and you get the idea of what
you're looking for. Do you feel like
you've been listened to is this is the
type of player I want to do I want to
run my offense?
Not really I mean it it doesn't really
work that way.
It really there are pieces like that I I
take that back. I
there are elements of what you may need
from a
position.
What type of tight end for instance do
you want a full back?
You're going to be an 11 personnel team
so personnel wise much more than
maybe the player cuz I don't think the
the parts that make a player how they're
wired their toughness mental toughness
you know, their self-awareness
do they love to practice do they love
football? I think that's from the jump
that's who you want to surround yourself
with.
So but maybe a little bit in terms of
how you see usage of a player it does
you no good to take a player without a
plan for them.
And I think we all saw Casey the same
way how we could utilize him.
I think we all saw it the same way in
terms of Denzel.
I think you know, when you talk about
the offensive lineman you're just trying
to get some guys that you think um
can play tackle but also have position
flex. I think that's the best way to go
about it. Speaking of fullbacks do do
you and your staff still consider Adrian
Colbert
a viable fullback
or tight end?
Well, it's funny the first time I saw
him I'm like you're the fullback here
right? You know, and he looked at me
like you know, no I'm a defensive
tackle. So that didn't go over great the
first conversation I had with him. I'm
joking he was he was fine but ultimately
you know, he's going to want to play
defensive tackle first but he's
certainly
um showed some promise in the backfield
and obviously has
um
the toughness and the want to and you
can see that on special teams he played
on special teams you could see him on
kickoff. So I do think that is an option
as we move forward but
again I think depending on how much
you're going to use that position, which
will
as we go along, we'll find out.
It's hard if you're going to be a 21
personnel team to have a part-time
fullback. So, you're we're going to have
to make that decision. Is it is it
situationally is it situation only?
You know, or you're only talking about a
little piece, maybe goal line short
yardage, or is it more than that? Is it
a normal rundown piece? And if it is,
then we're going to need more than a
part-time fullback. Did you get a chance
to watch the last two um
practice
Go. Go ahead.
We didn't get to watch the last two
practices of mini camp, just the first
one, obviously.
Um so, can I mean, can you kind of share
how how did Deshaun and and Shedeur and
and Dylan look in getting Now you got
all We just couldn't get past the draft
and get right on to to back the
quarterback. Everybody got some Miles
questions too while we're at it. I mean,
hell. Um uh we're just, you know, here
at night. Um first off, I'll address the
question. First of all, it was awesome.
3 days, the weather was unbelievable
to get out on the grass and pump the
music and get fired up being together,
and the neighbors complained, and we
didn't care, and we pumped up the music
louder. If they don't like it, they can
move. And so, we I didn't care. And it
was like, you know, being out there with
the guys and just getting a little bit
of a feel for who we have
uh on our roster
and I thought all three quarterbacks at
times you could see
you know, the positives in their game.
And learning the new system, and they've
been awesome in the meeting rooms and
and on the field, and uh it was just
kind of dipping our toe in the water,
but I thought
you know, Deshaun looked really good at
times, and there's other things he's got
to work on. Same with Shedeur and uh
with Dylan. So, I didn't really didn't
do a deep dive into all of them, but it
was a heck of a lot of fun being out
there, I can tell you that.
Upstairs, sitting next to Andrew in the
room. Um
you know,
you know, what's that been like for you
as a head coach? And
uh
you you and Andrew are, you know, find
yourselves thinking alike as as the
board comes together as you're sitting
next to each other? Well,
I think we see
players the same way in their value.
How they're wired. That part of it is
for sure.
Other than that, I just have a small
like
picture of each player. I certainly
don't have the picture of
every single player that they do, that
they've spent years, at least 1 year,
and probably more than that on a player.
So, what I do know is the players that I
did look at,
and I listen to the scouts,
and we all talk about how they're wired,
and
do we want them representing the
Cleveland Browns? Is that who we want?
And we've got a great group. We're just
continually trying to raise the floor,
but
I've been
thoroughly impressed with the process
of Andrew and his staff,
and
I can see
how the picks came to fruition last year
with the talent that we have, and I I
feel really good about what we're adding
at this point. When it comes to
Emmanuel, did you really want to play a
bunch of three safety packages?
Not really going to get into what we're
going to do um considering we won't have
film yet for our first game. So, we're
just fired up to have him.
To go back to the receivers, I know when
we first talked about your offense and
this offense's identity, talked about
scoring being the most paramount thing.
Like, do you feel good about the
different ways those guys can score
effectively at it so far?
I do. Um
again, like I said, I think they
complement each other.
I think it started with we had to
address the offensive line. I mean,
that's
you know, in both areas. That's, you
know, the receiver position and and the
offensive line, and I really feel good
about you know, where we're at at this
point.
Good.
Last one, Andrew, and that is
uh you know, in getting your evaluation
of how the quarterbacks looked,
there are still plenty left on the board
on the final day of the draft. Do you
Andrew has talked about it's wholly
realistic you guys could add another
quarterback to the room. Would you be
kind of excited to do that? And do you
see are there some guys that you like
from the quarterback position? We'll see
how it plays out. I don't think there's
any position
that is off the board that we wouldn't
take. Even after taking two receivers,
I've
we might have taken a third. We might
take another offensive lineman.
Um could be a quarterback. I don't think
there's any position when I left the
um
you know, the draft room that that I
didn't see anything that wouldn't, you
know, that wouldn't interest us at any
position.